KARAN DARYANI

Mob No: - +91 7043637071

E-Mail: - karandaryani22895@gmail.com

Location:- Ahmedabad, Gujarat

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Seeking a challenging and responsible position in a large and professional organization where, I will have the opportunity to make a positive contribution to business growth and to achieve personal development and career advancement, where it would strongly help in motivating my capabilities to fully prove my worth and my soon-to-be team to a substantial performance. Prepared and eager to take on a new responsibility.

ABOUT ME

I'm a Customer service representative with Cross-functional experience in the areas of:-

Process improvement, Quality assurance, I.T/Non-I.T Recruitment, Human Resource & Business Process Improvement, Client Relationship Management, Team Management, Training & Development, Reporting, Negotiation, Vendor Management, and Operational Activities.

Software: MES, Qlickview, MS office

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TTEC

Customer Support Executive

Sep 2022 - Present

- Responding to customer questions and complaints, and walking customers through basic troubleshooting.
- Maintaining a positive, empathetic, and professional attitude toward customers at all times.
- Responding promptly to customer inquiries.
- Communicating with customers through various channels.
- Acknowledging and resolving customer complaints.
- Knowing our products inside and out so that you can answer questions.
- Processing orders, forms, applications, and requests.
- Keeping records of customer interactions, transactions, comments, and complaints.
- Communicating and coordinating with colleagues as necessary.
- Providing feedback on the efficiency of the customer service process.
- Ensure customer satisfaction and provide professional customer support.

IMS People Possible

Technical Recruiter.

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022

- Role of Technical recruiter and Responsible for managing full life cycle recruiting process for all levels of management.
- Build the relationship with vendors regarding Candidates' requirements, a strong vendor Management experience.
- Submitting resumes to Team Head, Account managers, or Business Development team for submission to clients.
- Full life cycle Recruiting experience, understanding the opening, sourcing the right candidate, technical

interviews, negotiations, and closing the deal.

- Maintaining the relationship with clients, consultants, and vendors.
- Very strong experience in rate negotiation with consultants for almost all types of rates/salary like a contract W2, contract to Hire W2, Full time, Contract Independent.
- Proficient at successful sourcing of candidates via Internet sources and online resume database.
- Sourcing/tracking the resumes from Monster/ Dice/ Career Builder and other job portals.
- Scheduling phone, Skype, and face-to-face interviews of consultants anywhere in the U.S.
- Developing and maintaining a good relationship with consultants for Information, business, and leads.
- Carrying out prescreen, Coding test and scheduling interviews for Software engineers and IT professionals for big tech clients.

Netafim Irrigation, Vadodara Gujarat Production Engineer

July 2017 - Jan 2022

ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITY: -

- Handle extruders for executing production plan as received from planning department.
- Ensure quick set up time for product change during routine start up.
- Maintain raw material and semi processed material flow in shop floor.
- Maintain wall thickness of pipes as standard defined by QC and keeps track of material usage.
- Maintain production speed to achieve efficiency and better utilization of machines.
- Deploy the manpower on each line as per requirement of shift.
- Coordinate with maintenance team to achieve zero down time.
- Execute routine line maintenance schedules through teammates production functionaries, coordinate with Maintenance team for preventive and break down maintenance.
- Minimize quality scrap, hence contribute towards improving overall production and quality cost.
- Implement corrective and preventive action as per customer complaint and rejections.
- ISO Compliance records maintenance.
- Ensure that production processes related Safety (plant and people) standards are maintained and complied with, support for environmental conservation by efficient usage of resources like water, compressed air, raw material, spillage, wastages etc.
- Ensure adherence to safety and environmental aspects.
- Create 5S system in shop floor and implement lean projects.
- Deliver continuous improvement in system and process for productivity and cost savings.
- Train new employees in extrusion process and engage them effectively in production.
- Conduct meeting with shift people and discus about production metrics.

Lean Management & Operation Excellence

- Initiate and execute improvements in process and machineries
- Execute lean management system in the Department and measure the productivity
- Create SOP's and SWI's for process improvement & safety compliance
- Performed SMED for Product change for reduction of Downtime and Scrap

- Part of Kaizen team for process improvement of reuse of recycle material
- Regular checking of stock consumption and ensure minimum stock level in store.
- Analyze maintenance related data

Safety Management

- Ensure safety at shop floor and overall working area
- Conducted Toolbox talk to create awareness regarding the safety compliance
- Ensure use of PPE's while working
- Conducted training for machine operators for safe & healthy work environment
- Ensure the implementation of Lockout/Tag out while machine maintenance

Legal & ISO Compliance

- Maintain ISO related documents and meet the objectives ISO 9001 & 14001.
- Internal audits to maintain various ISO standards

Education

B.E in Plastic Technology (Gujarat Technological University) L.D College of Engineering 2013-2017